Guide to the Records of the Institute of African American Affairs RG.9.8
New York University Archives
- Series II: Association for Education in Journalism (AEJ)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Asselin, Charles, A+, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Braithwaite, Colleen R., A-, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Brooks, Rodney, A-, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Burton, Charlene F., A+, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Calahan, Hortense C. A+, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Cerna, Henry James, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Prentice Favors, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - French, Roberta, A++, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Jones, Wendy Dianna, A-, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Richardson, Kenneth, B+, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Thompson, Rodney, A, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Marshall Boyd, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Donna Britt, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Aubrey Calloway, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; James Hadley, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Cecilian Fernandez, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Gazelia Payne, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Tonya Widemon, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Joseph Fugett, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Sandra Gregg, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Valerie Kersey, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Raymond Patterson, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Debra Marie Martin, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Robert Palomares, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Velma Thomas, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Sheilah Diane Vance, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence AEJ (1), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence AEJ (2), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226027 6
  - Final Report AEJ, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Finances AEJ, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Forms AEJ, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous - AEJ, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Ronald Daise, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Sundra Escott, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Lydia Gardner, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Mr. Tracey Gibson, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Sheryl Hilliard, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Kenneth Myers, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Roslyn Smackum, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: M. Patricia Yu, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (1), 1978 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (2), 1978 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - AEJ Interns: Abdul-Azeez, Suleiman, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - AEJ Interns: Branch, George E., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - AEJ Interns: Cage, Mary, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - AEJ Interns: Clayton, Gail, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - AEJ Interns: Dannells, Vernyce, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - AEJ Interns: Duckett, Joy, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - AEJ Interns: Morgan, Viola J., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - AEJ Interns: Navarro, Mireya, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - AEJ Interns: Owens, Previa M., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - AEJ Interns: Robinson, Glynis, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - AEJ Interns: Robotham, Rosemarie, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - AEJ Interns: Saxon, Janet, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (1), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (2), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226028 4
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Anderson, Janet M., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Anderson, Kathy Renee, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Beach-Wilson, Gladys, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Brown, William T., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Camara, Sajo M., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Carkum, Shelly, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Greth, Carlos, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Gwynn, Kathy L., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Lecoints, Gertrude, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Leonard, Lori A., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Magubane, Vukani, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Shields, Audrey D., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Smith, Robina S., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Utsey, Keith J., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Wright, Winford C., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Vazquez, Carmen A., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (1), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (2), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (3), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Program Operation - AEJ (1), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Program Operation - AEJ (2), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Finalists: Alleyne, Celeste, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Finalists: Bailey, Michael, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Finalists: Horn, Ginnie, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Finalists: Johnson, Cheryl, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Finalists: Johnson, Michelle, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Finalists: Marrs, Judith, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Finalists: Moorehead, Eric, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Finalists: Pilcher, Delores, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Finalists: Szto, Mary Christine, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Finalists: Villarosa, Linda, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Finalists: Williams, Kelly, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (1), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226029 2
  - Program Administration - AEJ, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Interns: Gordon Balkcom, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Interns: Jones, Michael, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Interns: Martinez, Marcos, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Interns: Reeves, Crystal, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Interns: Roberts, Sandra, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Interns: Rogers, Danita, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Interns: Rodriguez, (Jaime) Javier, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Interns: Tracey, Aldina, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Interns: Trouth, Audrey, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Interns: Tuitt, Ronnie, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Finances- AEJ, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Interns: Ashley, Berchelle D., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Interns: Lily Berjano, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Interns: Lisa Bellamy, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Interns: Lisa Godley, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Interns: Jones, Carla, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Interns: Thomas, Larry, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Interns: Yvette Walker, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Interns: Adrine, E. Marie, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Interns: Collison, Michele, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Interns: Goeude, Nicholas, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Interns: Hom, Genevieve, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Interns: Miller, Deborah, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Interns: Seymore, Kelly, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Interns: Carol Bash, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Interns: Valerie Boyd, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Interns: Leslie Doi, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Interns: Farah Griffin, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Interns: Joye E. Mercer, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Interns: Winifred Yu, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Interns: Lisa V. Bond, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Interns: Adrienne Johnson, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Interns: Roberto Santiago, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Interns: Angela L. Slaughter, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Interns: Wanda Renea Taylor, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Interns: Vivian S. Toy, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - AEJ Correspondence, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226030 0
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Interns: Lisa Best, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Interns: Karen Brailsford, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Interns: Crystal Hayling, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Interns: John C. Hopkins, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Interns: Lisa Lewis, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Interns: Mai-Lan Pham, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Interns: Inez Pinto, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Interns: Constance White, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Interns: Fredricka Whitfield, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Interns: Loretta Williams, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Finalists/Interns: Jennifer Borum, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Finalists/Interns: Stephanie Esters, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Finalists/Interns: Ernie Freeman, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Finalists/Interns: Goodwin, Jesse, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Finalists/Interns: Tyrone Guiden, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Finalists/Interns: James, Alva Marie, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Finalists/Interns: Jeffries, Ira L., 1986 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Finalists/Interns: Juanita Poe, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Finalists/Interns: Salter, Allanah, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Finalists/Interns: Tassey, Elaine F., 1986 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Finalists/Interns: Turner, Dawn, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Finalists: Karen E. Delgado, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Finalists: Sheridan Honore, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Finalists: Pennie Lee, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Finalists: Allison Louis, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Finalists: Annette Shaw, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Finalists: Smith, Kimberleigh, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Finalists: Ayesha Wilson, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Finalists: Janet Jun-Lien Wong, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Finalists: Charisse K. Lawrence, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Finalists: John Yeh, AEJMC Applicant, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Finalists/Interns: Kalena Hammock, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Finalists/Interns: Natasha M. Labaze, AEJMC Applicant, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Finalists/Interns: Michael Edwin Watson, AEJMC Applicant, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Finalists/Interns: Towanda Underdue, AEJMC, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Kimetris Baltrip, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226031 8
  - AEJMC Applicant: Efrem Keir Graham, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Tanya Haughton, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Elizabeth R. Mesa, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Tara Roberts, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Andrea Wiggins, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Lisa Chin, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Cheryl Hendricks, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Sirena Huang, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Kimberly Maxwell, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Raoul Mowatt, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Teresa C. Puente, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Dara N. Shariff, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Towanda Underdue, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Valentina Wilson, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Geraldine Alumit, AEJ, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Marisol Bello, AEJ, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Melinda A. Bond, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Stacy Coates, AEJ, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Alicia Coulote, AEJ, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Cora Daniels, AEJ, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Heidi W. Durrow, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Patricia Edwards, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Grace Kyungwon Hong, AEJ, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Sophia V. McGregor, AEJ, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Kimberly R. Riley, AEJ, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Jennifer Rodriguez, AEJ, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Series III: Earl S. Davis Correspondence
  - ABFA, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - ABFA - Confidential For Adm. Report, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - M.L.King, Jan 15, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - African Materials, Nov 1990 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - African Global Heritage Assoc., Dec 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - AMC - Colleagues Grp., May 8, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226032 6
  - Assoc. Black Women in Higher Education, Jun 4, 1905 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Black Alumni - Call in list, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Black Creation, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Black Student Center, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Black Family Conference, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Untitled [approximately 2 linear inches of unfoldered materials (IAAA personnel information, correspondence, articles, flyers, etc.); folder provided], undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Untitled [includes material on African Panorama, correspondence, and articles], undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Events, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Resource Network, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Dr. Elizabeth Henshaw, Visiting Professorship - Exchange, Dec 3, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Elizabeth Henshaw - Nigeria [EMPTY], undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Franco, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Hutchins, Annette, Oct 16, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - IAAA Advisory Minutes, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - IAAA History, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - IAAA Annual Reports, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Orde Coombs Collection, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226033 4
  - Rod Rogers Dance Company, Mar 29, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Soul of Reason - Interview Questions, Feb. 1978- Nov 1978 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Soul of Reason - Interview Questions, Nov 1978-Jul 1979 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Untitled [approximately 1 lin. inch of unfoldered material (NYU Purchasing; correspondence; "The Black Woman and the Bicentennial Conference, June 24-27, 1976," packet and notes); folder provided] (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - [Non-NYU Publications], undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Six Annual Community Service Award and Tribute, Jun 21, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Resource Network's Day Tour of Harlem, Jun 22, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Lecture: "African History: An African Perspective" by Dr. Albert Adu Boahem, Oct 9, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Lecture/Reception: "Strengthening the Bond Between People of African Heritage", Oct 14, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - ABFAS Open House Reception, Oct 16, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Lecture: "Forging Connections: African American/African Caribbean", Nov 13, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - The NYC 1992 Media Conference: "Accessing the Media in NYC"(3 folders), Feb 5, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Tisch S.O.A. Black and Hispanic Film Festival(3 folders), Feb 18, 1992-Feb 25, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Annual Choral Celebration of Black History-NYU All University Gospel Choir, Feb 20, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Black History Month Celebration at the Bedford Stuyvesant Community Mental Health Center, Inc. Keynote: Earl Davis, Feb 25, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Lecture/Reception: "An Evening With The Elders", Feb 27, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - "Women As a Catalyst For Social Change" Lecture by Mrs. Coretta Scott King, Mar 9, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - NYU Black Lobby Day trip to Albany, Mar 17, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226034 2
  - NYU Black Lobby Day trip to Albany, Mar 17, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - NYU Black Lobby Day trip to Albany, Mar 17, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - NYU Black Lobby Day trip to Albany, Mar 17, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - The 54th Massachusetts Colored Infantry Lecture by Jacqueline Shearer and Professor Thelma Foote, Apr 23, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Black and Latino Awards Ceremony, May 2, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Welcome Reception for Dr. Manthia Diawara, Sep 18, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - The Coalition for Columbus on Trial; "500 Years of Cultural Resistance" and a Prayer March to the Negro Burial Site, Oct 1, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - The 1992 Christopher Columbus Consortium, NY Presents COLVMBVS RECONCILIATION FORVM: "THE WELL BEING IN THE XXIrst CENTURY.", Oct 9, 1992-Oct 11, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Christopher Columbus Consortium: Dr. Sandra Dernini, Jan 1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226035 9
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - "The Herencia Latina" November Celebration-Concert at Loeb Center: featuring Willie Colon and His Legal Alien Band, Nov 6, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Movie: "Passin It on" -- A Documentary Film About Dhoruba Bin Wahad and the Black Panther Part, Dec 5, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - James Weldon Johnson, Nov 12, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Nigerian National Culture Group, Jul 8, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - National Conference of Artists, Apr 5, 1994-Apr 11, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Black Theater in America, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - NY Urban Coalition Educational Summit, Dec 12, 1993-Dec 13, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Festac Reunion, Apr 11, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Black Articles, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Black Articles, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Black Literary, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Conference on African and African American Studies in Atlanta, GA, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence of Roscoe Brown, Director-IAAA, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226036 7
  - IAAA Alteration of Office, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - IAAA Background Information, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - IAAA Background Information, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - IAAA Background Information, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - IAAA Background Information, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - IAAA Fundraising, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - IAAA Lecture/Seminar Report and Evaluation, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - IAAA Organizational Proposal Correspondence, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - IAAA Organizational Proposal, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Progress Report, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - IAAA Progress Report, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Center Correspondence, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Organizational Proposal for an Afro-American Institute at NYU In Honor of the Late Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Publications-NYU: The Black Student at NYU, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - X, Malcolm Research Tape Transcription, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - X, Malcolm Research Tape Transcription, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - X, Malcolm Research Tape Transcription, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - X, Malcolm Research Tape Transcription, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - X, Malcolm Research Tape Transcription, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - X, Malcolm Research Tape Transcription, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Black Articles, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Black Creation Magazine, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Black History Book Project, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Black History Book Project, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Black Studies Coordinating Council, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Black Studies Courses, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, Roscoe Brown, IAAA Dir., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Democratic Republic of the Congo, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - IAAA Activities, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - IAAA Advisory Board, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Billings, Charles E., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 36)